[{"answer": "Because... there was no way to win", "docId": "Star-Trek-II-The-Wrath-of-Khan.txt", "asentId": 3, "question": "... No, sir. It has not", "qsentId": 2}, {"answer": "How we deal with death is at least as important as how we deal with life, wouldn't you say", "docId": "Star-Trek-II-The-Wrath-of-Khan.txt", "asentId": 5, "question": "Then you have something new to think about. Carry on", "qsentId": 4}, {"answer": "scenario frequently wreaks havoc with students and equipment.  As I recall you took the test three times yourself. Your final solution was, shall we say, unique", "docId": "Star-Trek-II-The-Wrath-of-Khan.txt", "asentId": 7, "question": "Yours was not a solution which would have occurred to a Vulcan mentality", "qsentId": 6}, {"answer": "I know of your fondness for antiques", "docId": "Star-Trek-II-The-Wrath-of-Khan.txt", "asentId": 9, "question": "None of which I am consciously aware", "qsentId": 8}, {"answer": " Mr. my friend, you old space dog. You're well", "docId": "Star-Trek-II-The-Wrath-of-Khan.txt", "asentId": 11, "question": "Oh? A wee bout of what, Mr. my friend", "qsentId": 10}, {"answer": "Every young boy's fancy. I seem to remember it myself.  Very well. Mr. my friend, are your engines capable of handling a minor training cruise", "docId": "Star-Trek-II-The-Wrath-of-Khan.txt", "asentId": 13, "question": "Mr. my friend, the word is given", "qsentId": 12}, {"answer": "Repeat... what's wrong? What's wrong", "docId": "Star-Trek-II-The-Wrath-of-Khan.txt", "asentId": 15, "question": "Taking my friend? Who? Who is taking my friend", "qsentId": 14}, {"answer": "... Please help us, my friend... won't let them have... without proper... repeat... on whose authority..", "docId": "Star-Trek-II-The-Wrath-of-Khan.txt", "asentId": 17, "question": "my friend please", "qsentId": 16}, {"answer": "my friend", "docId": "Star-Trek-II-The-Wrath-of-Khan.txt", "asentId": 19, "question": "We don't have minutes. Can you give me phaser power", "qsentId": 18}, {"answer": "Don't play with me, my friend, my hand is on the phaser control", "docId": "Star-Trek-II-The-Wrath-of-Khan.txt", "asentId": 21, "question": "I give you sixty seconds, Admiral", "qsentId": 20}, {"answer": "Sensors, Captain", "docId": "Star-Trek-II-The-Wrath-of-Khan.txt", "asentId": 23, "question": "And no way of knowing if Reliant is still in the area..", "qsentId": 22}, {"answer": "I suppose I was.  I poured a drink. Would you like it", "docId": "Star-Trek-II-The-Wrath-of-Khan.txt", "asentId": 25, "question": " I didn't expect anything", "qsentId": 24}, {"answer": "I'm trying, my friend", "docId": "Star-Trek-II-The-Wrath-of-Khan.txt", "asentId": 27, "question": "I am truly sorry", "qsentId": 26}]